

NIV/NII IInitad Stata

SUMMARY

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Customer-oriented, strategic-thinking sales management professional successful in cultivating partnerships, retaining top accounts, and growing profit channels. Multi-tasking and self-motivated leader with expertise in expanding network connections and persuasively introducing products. Well-versed in implementing pricing models, managing vendor relations and expanding territory.

SKILLS

- Customer presentations
- Business support software proficiency
- Market and competitive analysis
- Budgeting and P&L
- Sales tracking
- Profit and revenue-generating strategies
- Market intelligence

- General sales techniques
- Excellent communication skills
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Market research, forecasting and analysis
- Persuasive negotiations

EXPERIENCE

VP HEAD OF GLOBAL SALES & ENTERPRISE RETAIL | 04/2019 to Current CITCON - New-York, United States

- Provided professional services and support in a dynamic work environment.
- Managed time efficiently in order to complete all tasks within deadlines.
- Scheduled meetings with employees to address concerns and grievances.
- Managed compensation, insurance, and vacation days within employee benefits programs.
- Assisted in employee recruitment, hiring, and interview processes.

VP HEAD OF MERCHANT OPERATIONS EXCELLENCE | 08/2020 to 01/2021 CITCON - New-York, United States

- Participated in team projects, demonstrating an ability to work collaboratively and effectively.
- Proven ability to learn quickly and adapt to new situations.
- Used excellent verbal skills to engage customers in conversation and effectively determine needs and requirements.
- Provided leadership, insight and mentoring to newly hired employees to supply knowledge of various company programs.

VP, ENTERPRISE & RETAIL GENERAL MANAGER | 10/2018 to 08/2019 CITCON - New-York, United States

- Aligned organizational objectives with the company mission to increase business growth and integrate work strategies.
- Identified problems and implemented solutions to better streamline operations.
- Increased company growth through collaboration with sales and marketing departments.
- Partnered with global business heads to lead deployment training.

VP SALES & ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT NORTH-AMERICA | 06/2018 to 04/2019 CITCON - New-York, United States

- Developed short and long-term sales strategies to gain market share, uncover new sales
 opportunities and increase revenue.
- Increased revenue by implementing effective sales strategies in the sales cycle process from prospecting leads through close.
- Led learning and development initiatives to educate sales personnel on new products and services.

 Analyzed competitive environment and customer procurement trends to support growth strategies.

GENERAL MANAGER US EAST & CANADA | 06/2017 to 04/2019

CITCON - New-York, United States

- Organized and detail-oriented with a strong work ethic.
- Used strong analytical and problem-solving skills to develop effective solutions for challenging situations.
- Directed or coordinated financial or budget activities to fund operations and maximize investments.
- Mitigated business risks by working closely with staff members and assessing performance.

DIRECTOR PRODUCT & MARKETING NORTH-AMERICA | 04/2016 to 07/2017 LION TRAVEL SERVICE CO., LTD - Taipei, Taiwan

- Trained staff in the operation and upkeep of equipment.
- Evaluated projects for required production resources
- Evaluated marketing personnel and offered constructive feedback on ways to improve.
- Recommended policy changes to improve marketing tactics and strategies.

OTHER PROFESSIONAL OCCUPATIONS

MEMBER AND SPEAKER | 01/2018 to Current

Merchant Advisory Group - Minneapolis, Minnesota

- Developed marketing campaigns for environmental technologies or services.
- Posted and updated content on the company's website and social media outlets.
- Implemented stories and anecdotes into speeches to make information more entertaining.
- Drafted speeches to persuade or entertain the audience.

MEMBER | 11/2017 to Current

French Founders - New-York, United States

- Worked flexible hours across the night, weekend, and holiday shifts.
- Devised organizational vision, mission and foundational structure to facilitate early growth.
- Excellent communication skills, both verbal and written.
- Delivered speeches and attended industry conferences to promote company image and engage with buyers.

EDUCATION

ESSCA - Grande École In Angers, France

M.D

Major: Mass Retail Marketing, 2006

National Sun Yat-Sen University - Public University In Kaohsiung, Taiwan M.D.

Exchange Program Management, 2005

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

University of California, Berkely

Bitcoin and Cryptocurrencies, 2021

The University of Hong Kong

Introduction to FinTech, 2019

Harvard University

Political and Intellectual Foundations, 2016

Lion Travel Academy - Taiwan

Lion Travel Talent Manager, 2011

PERSONAL

Sports

Soccer, Hockey (drafted to Senior on my first Junior year) and Xtrem Sports (was sponsored in Taiwan)

Reserve Officer, French Navy

Included seminar at West Point

Multilingual

French (Native), English (fluent), Mandarin (fluent), Spanish (conversation)